<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Principle on Floyd</title><link>https://hightower.space/tags/principle/</link><description>Recent content in Principle on Floyd</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://hightower.space/tags/principle/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>GCP PDE Exam Principles</title><link>https://hightower.space/posts/gcp-pde-exam-principles/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hightower.space/posts/gcp-pde-exam-principles/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="intro">Intro&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>This is a post in a series recording some notes as I&amp;rsquo;m studying for &lt;a href="https://cloud.google.com/certification/data-engineer">Google&amp;rsquo;s Professional Data Engineer Certification&lt;/a>.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>In this post, I provide some principles I am keeping in mind as I prepare for the exam.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="disclaimer">Disclaimer&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Please read &lt;a href="https://hightower.space/posts/gcp-notes-disclaimer/">this disclaimer&lt;/a>.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="gcp-pde-exam-principles">GCP PDE Exam Principles&lt;/h2>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>[security] Follow the &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Principle_of_least_privilege">Principle of Least Privilege&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
&lt;li>When between multiple options, the simplest answer is probably right&lt;/li>
&lt;li>When between multiple options, the cheapest answer is probably right&lt;/li>
&lt;li>An answer&amp;rsquo;s complexity is likely proporitional to the questions&amp;rsquo; complexity
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>For example, simple questions like: &amp;ldquo;What is your favorite colour&amp;rdquo; probably has a simple answer&lt;/li>
&lt;li>A more complex question (e.g. &amp;ldquo;What is the Air-Speed Velocity of an Unladen Swallow on a Tuesday in a head-wind of 30 kmph and 70% relative humidity&amp;rdquo;) probably requires a more complex answer&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>When creating Bigtable row keys, the key focus is to avoid hot spots
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>DON&amp;rsquo;T USE timestamp as start of rowkey for bigtable&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Prefer pre-trained ML models to custom-trained
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>These solutions are typically good enough for basic use-cases and can be implemented more quickly&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>[security] Assign roles to groups and add users to groups (don&amp;rsquo;t apply roles to users)&lt;/li>
&lt;li>If something is self-joined and running into problems when scaling, the answer likely involves normalizing&lt;/li>
&lt;li>If question mentions &amp;ldquo;realtime&amp;rdquo; and pub/sub, it probably requires a &lt;em>push&lt;/em> from pub/sub rather than a pull&lt;/li>
&lt;li>[BQ] W/ multiple, wildcard tables, &lt;em>partitioning&lt;/em> is best (over sharding)&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Typically, serverless/cloud-native solution is favorable over managed services or dedicated machines/VMs&lt;/li>
&lt;li>HDFS files should be stored in GCS&lt;/li>
&lt;li>It is not uncommon for multiple services to be used together (b/c each service is often optimized to do one thing very well)&lt;/li>
&lt;li>If the question involves &amp;ldquo;ANSI SQL&amp;rdquo;, the answer probably involves BigQuery&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul></description></item><item><title>Rome Wasn't Built in a Day</title><link>https://hightower.space/posts/great-things-take-time/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hightower.space/posts/great-things-take-time/</guid><description>&lt;p>I could say a lot on this subject, but for now, I&amp;rsquo;ll make this quick (which is ironic in light of the topic at hand). I believe that &lt;strong>doing things of great value takes time.&lt;/strong> This applies to software, research, education, business, relationships, sports, and every area of life. I experience this reality on a daily basis as my passion is writing software. Good software and powerful tools just take time to design, develop, and refine. For me, ideas often come in virtually instantaneous flashes of insight, but it takes a lot more time to make those ideas a reality and one has to be willing to invest time. One of the first things I tell anyone who asks me how to learn a programming language is that it will take time. Work like crazy and cover as much ground as you can, but realize that it will still take time. Even at a high velocity, it still takes light around 8 minutes to go from the sun to the earth. No matter how &amp;lsquo;fast&amp;rsquo; or &amp;lsquo;smart&amp;rsquo; you are, things of great value take time.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>To be clear, I&amp;rsquo;m not saying we should expect slowness or that we should acquiesce to broken processes which waste our time, but don&amp;rsquo;t go through life thinking you will accomplish great things overnight. Give it time! Rome wasn&amp;rsquo;t built in a day.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Let Your Ideas See the Light of Day</title><link>https://hightower.space/posts/light-of-day/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hightower.space/posts/light-of-day/</guid><description>&lt;p>It is a deeply held principle of mine that beliefs and ideas are strongest when they have been tested and exposed to the proverbial &amp;rsquo;light of day&amp;rsquo;. We have a tendency to cloister our beliefs and new ideas within the comfortable walls of our own minds. When we do this, we are missing out on the criticism, critique, and dialog that makes ideas powerful and robust.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Ideas which are not exposed to the real world are like a cardboard box; they can withstand minimal pressure from certain directions, but are not ready to hold up the weight of careful scrutiny. Powerful, world-changing ideas are like gold or diamonds; they are formed by strenuous, uncomfortable processes over time. This is why I try to expose my ideas to the light of day rather than keeping them hidden in my mind. I want to think powerful, world-changing thoughts and I can&amp;rsquo;t do that on my own.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>