<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Principle on Floyd Hightower</title><link>https://hightower.space/tags/principle/</link><description>Recent content in Principle on Floyd Hightower</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://hightower.space/tags/principle/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>GCP PDE Exam Principles</title><link>https://hightower.space/posts/gcp-pde-exam-principles/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hightower.space/posts/gcp-pde-exam-principles/</guid><description>Intro This is a post in a series recording some notes as I&amp;rsquo;m studying for Google&amp;rsquo;s Professional Data Engineer Certification.
In this post, I provide some principles I am keeping in mind as I prepare for the exam.
Disclaimer Please read this disclaimer.
GCP PDE Exam Principles [security] Follow the Principle of Least Privilege When between multiple options, the simplest answer is probably right When between multiple options, the cheapest answer is probably right An answer&amp;rsquo;s complexity is likely proporitional to the questions&amp;rsquo; complexity For example, simple questions like: &amp;ldquo;What is your favorite colour&amp;rdquo; probably has a simple answer A more complex question (e.</description></item><item><title>Rome Wasn't Built in a Day</title><link>https://hightower.space/posts/great-things-take-time/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hightower.space/posts/great-things-take-time/</guid><description>I could say a lot on this subject, but for now, I&amp;rsquo;ll make this quick (which is ironic in light of the topic at hand). I believe that doing things of great value takes time. This applies to software, research, education, business, relationships, sports, and every area of life. I experience this reality on a daily basis as my passion is writing software. Good software and powerful tools just take time to design, develop, and refine.</description></item><item><title>Let Your Ideas See the Light of Day</title><link>https://hightower.space/posts/light-of-day/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hightower.space/posts/light-of-day/</guid><description>It is a deeply held principle of mine that beliefs and ideas are strongest when they have been tested and exposed to the proverbial &amp;rsquo;light of day&amp;rsquo;. We have a tendency to cloister our beliefs and new ideas within the comfortable walls of our own minds. When we do this, we are missing out on the criticism, critique, and dialog that makes ideas powerful and robust.
Ideas which are not exposed to the real world are like a cardboard box; they can withstand minimal pressure from certain directions, but are not ready to hold up the weight of careful scrutiny.</description></item></channel></rss>