<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Google Cloud on Floyd Hightower</title><link>https://hightower.space/tags/google-cloud/</link><description>Recent content in Google Cloud on Floyd Hightower</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://hightower.space/tags/google-cloud/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>GCP Databases in a Nutshell</title><link>https://hightower.space/posts/gcp-pde-database-notes/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hightower.space/posts/gcp-pde-database-notes/</guid><description>Intro This post is part of a series of posts with notes as I&amp;rsquo;m studying for Google&amp;rsquo;s Professional Data Engineer Certification.
This particular post covers Cloud Composer in a nutshell.
Disclaimer Please read this disclaimer.
Databases Grouped by Management Model Managed Services Cloud SQL Cloud Spanner Cloud Bigtable Serverless Services Cloud Storage Firestore Grouped by Size/Relationality Size of Data: Small Large Relational Cloud SQL Spanner* Non-Relational Firestore** Bigtable * The option of using processing units as the means of calculating cost for Spanner makes it a better option for smaller solutions ** Firestore can handle large amounts of data too when provisioned correctly, but it can be used for small applications where-as Bigtable really isn&amp;rsquo;t/shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be used for small use-cases</description></item><item><title>ML for the GCP PDE Exam</title><link>https://hightower.space/posts/gcp-pde-ml-notes/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hightower.space/posts/gcp-pde-ml-notes/</guid><description>Intro This post is part of a series of posts with notes as I&amp;rsquo;m studying for Google&amp;rsquo;s Professional Data Engineer Certification.
This particular post covers ML topics.
Disclaimer Please read this disclaimer.
Key Concepts L1 vs. L2 regression: L1 estimates the median of the data using absolute value Reduces low-value features Robust to outliers Good when only certain features contribute to success of model L2 estimates the mean of the data to avoid overfitting Not recommended for feature selection Good when all features contribute relatively equally to the success of a model TensorFlow Know how TensorFlow can be deployed (also, cost vs.</description></item><item><title>Dataflow in a Nutshell</title><link>https://hightower.space/posts/dataflow-notes/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hightower.space/posts/dataflow-notes/</guid><description>Intro This post is part of a series of posts with notes as I&amp;rsquo;m studying for Google&amp;rsquo;s Professional Data Engineer Certification.
This particular post covers Dataflow in a nutshell.
Disclaimer Please read this disclaimer.
Dataflow Serverless Wraps apache beam Handles batch and streaming data Typically, more effecient scaling than Dataproc Therefore, it&amp;rsquo;s typically cheaper than Dataproc Used internally at Google Improved by Google over time Know about windowing fixed window in java/python ≈ tumbling in SQL sliding ≈ hoping in SQL session (is the same for both SQL and java/python) Know about watermarks</description></item><item><title>GCP PDE Exam Principles</title><link>https://hightower.space/posts/gcp-pde-exam-principles/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hightower.space/posts/gcp-pde-exam-principles/</guid><description>Intro This is a post in a series recording some notes as I&amp;rsquo;m studying for Google&amp;rsquo;s Professional Data Engineer Certification.
In this post, I provide some principles I am keeping in mind as I prepare for the exam.
Disclaimer Please read this disclaimer.
GCP PDE Exam Principles [security] Follow the Principle of Least Privilege When between multiple options, the simplest answer is probably right When between multiple options, the cheapest answer is probably right An answer&amp;rsquo;s complexity is likely proporitional to the questions&amp;rsquo; complexity For example, simple questions like: &amp;ldquo;What is your favorite colour&amp;rdquo; probably has a simple answer A more complex question (e.</description></item><item><title>GCP PDE Recipies</title><link>https://hightower.space/posts/gcp-pde-recipies/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hightower.space/posts/gcp-pde-recipies/</guid><description>Intro This is a post in a series recording some notes as I&amp;rsquo;m studying for Google&amp;rsquo;s Professional Data Engineer Certification.
In this post, I provide some common recipies which are commonly used in Google Cloud.
Disclaimer Please read this disclaimer.
GCP PDE Recipies The Classic Pub/Sub -&amp;gt; Dataflow -&amp;gt; BQ (batch inserts)
Variations:
Pub/Sub -&amp;gt; Dataflow -&amp;gt; BQ (streaming inserts) Pub/Sub -&amp;gt; Dataflow -&amp;gt; Bigtable -&amp;gt; BQ (querying Bigtable using federated query) For use-cases which require analytics and the low-latency afforded by Bigtable Uploading Data to Google Cloud gsutil on-prem.</description></item><item><title>BigQuery in a Nutshell</title><link>https://hightower.space/posts/bigquery-notes/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hightower.space/posts/bigquery-notes/</guid><description>Intro This post is part of a series of posts with notes as I&amp;rsquo;m studying for Google&amp;rsquo;s Professional Data Engineer Certification.
This particular post covers BigQuery in a nutshell.
Disclaimer Please read this disclaimer.
BigQuery Fully managed, petabyte-scale data warehouse/analysis service Has two components: Storage (built on &amp;ldquo;Colossus&amp;rdquo;) Query/Processing Engine Good for federated searching Column-based storage Allows ANSI SQL compliant queries Includes good support for: Building (basic) ML models Logistic regression - classifying categories Linear regression - forcasting # values GeoViz Structs Allows horizontal storage Look like: event.</description></item><item><title>Bigtable in a Nutshell</title><link>https://hightower.space/posts/bigtable-notes/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hightower.space/posts/bigtable-notes/</guid><description>Intro This post is part of a series of posts with notes as I&amp;rsquo;m studying for Google&amp;rsquo;s Professional Data Engineer Certification.
This particular post covers Bigtable in a nutshell.
Disclaimer Please read this disclaimer.
Bigtable h-base compliant Requires configuration and management of nodes Designing/choosing a good row-key (index) is critical to avoiding hot-spots (where some nodes have significantly more to process than others) Rows are sorted lexigraphically by row-key Generally a long, compound key (e.</description></item><item><title>Cloud Composer in a Nutshell</title><link>https://hightower.space/posts/cloud-composer-notes/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hightower.space/posts/cloud-composer-notes/</guid><description>Intro This post is part of a series of posts with notes as I&amp;rsquo;m studying for Google&amp;rsquo;s Professional Data Engineer Certification.
This particular post covers Cloud Composer in a nutshell.
Disclaimer Please read this disclaimer.
Cloud Composer Managed Apache Airflow Create DAGs (Directed Acyclic Graph) Scheduling: Periodic (pull) (specified in the Airflow GUI - e.g. every day at noon) Event-driven (push) (e.g. when new data is uploaded to GCS)</description></item><item><title>Cloud SQL in a Nutshell</title><link>https://hightower.space/posts/cloud-sql-notes/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hightower.space/posts/cloud-sql-notes/</guid><description>Intro This post is part of a series of posts with notes as I&amp;rsquo;m studying for Google&amp;rsquo;s Professional Data Engineer Certification.
This particular post covers Cloud SQL in a nutshell.
Disclaimer Please read this disclaimer.
Cloud SQL Offers: MySQL Postgres Micro$oft SQL server High Availability through data replication through zones in a region (and failover - there are VMs in each zone in case one fails) Can transition to Spanner pretty easily</description></item><item><title>Firestore in a Nutshell</title><link>https://hightower.space/posts/firestore-notes/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hightower.space/posts/firestore-notes/</guid><description>Intro This post is part of a series of posts with notes as I&amp;rsquo;m studying for Google&amp;rsquo;s Professional Data Engineer Certification.
This particular post covers Firestore in a nutshell.
Disclaimer Please read this disclaimer.
Firestore Similar to mongodb Store data as documents Rare to migrate to Bigtable (unlike Cloud SQL which may migrate to Spanner eventually) Web devs. like it and it has easy integration for web/mobile use-cases</description></item><item><title>GCP Notes Disclaimer</title><link>https://hightower.space/posts/gcp-notes-disclaimer/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hightower.space/posts/gcp-notes-disclaimer/</guid><description>Disclaimer You were likely linked to this post from a GCP note blog post.
This post is to warn you that the content of that post was written before I had taken the exam.
I do not guarantee the accuracy or long-term reliability of these notes.
Use them at your own risk and always defer to Google&amp;rsquo;s docs as canon.</description></item><item><title>Pub/Sub in a Nutshell</title><link>https://hightower.space/posts/pubsub-notes/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hightower.space/posts/pubsub-notes/</guid><description>Intro This post is part of a series of posts with notes as I&amp;rsquo;m studying for Google&amp;rsquo;s Professional Data Engineer Certification.
This particular post covers Pub/Sub in a nutshell.
Disclaimer Please read this disclaimer.
Pub/Sub Fully managed, data ingestion and distro. system Async., real-time message bus Good soln. for buffering changes for lightly-coupled architectures P/S decouples publishers and subscribers HIPPA compliant Stores data for up to 31 days Default is 7 days Has topics and subscriptions Data is published to a topic Subscriptions dictate who recieves content for which topics Relationship btw.</description></item><item><title>Spanner in a Nutshell</title><link>https://hightower.space/posts/spanner-notes/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hightower.space/posts/spanner-notes/</guid><description>Intro This post is part of a series of posts with notes as I&amp;rsquo;m studying for Google&amp;rsquo;s Professional Data Engineer Certification.
This particular post covers Spanner in a nutshell.
Disclaimer Please read this disclaimer.
Spanner Horizontally scalable No-ops Only change needed is to add nodes Add another node if CPU &amp;gt; 70-75% Each node can handle 1.5 - 2 TB Can create linked/embeded tables Helps avoid the cost of joins for normalized tables Two payment methods: Pay-by-node: standard method Pay-by-processing-unit: let&amp;rsquo;s you pay for more granular operations/scale 1 node = 1,000 processing units</description></item><item><title>Mapping GCP Products to Open-Source Systems</title><link>https://hightower.space/posts/gcp-to-oss-map/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hightower.space/posts/gcp-to-oss-map/</guid><description>Intro This is the first post in a series recording some notes as I&amp;rsquo;m studying for Google&amp;rsquo;s Professional Data Engineer Certification.
The plan is that each post will discuss a particular service, relevant to the GCP PDE cert.
Disclaimer Please read this disclaimer.
Mapping GCP Products to OSS I find it helpful to map GCP Products to open-source software systems used by each GCP product.
Here&amp;rsquo;s a table with my current understanding:</description></item><item><title>GCP Serverless Compute Options Overview</title><link>https://hightower.space/posts/gcp-serverless-compute-options/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hightower.space/posts/gcp-serverless-compute-options/</guid><description>Intro This is a brief overview of the Serverless Compute Options in GCP.
After reading this post, I hope you are:
Familiar with the main options (at a high-level) Understand some main use-cases for each option Have a limited understanding of what it looks like to work with a service in each product The google docs on these subjects are really helpful&amp;hellip; I strongly recommend reading through them.</description></item></channel></rss>