<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>List on Floyd Hightower</title><link>https://hightower.space/tags/list/</link><description>Recent content in List on Floyd Hightower</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://hightower.space/tags/list/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>2021 Reading List</title><link>https://hightower.space/reading-list/2021-reading-list/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hightower.space/reading-list/2021-reading-list/</guid><description>Books read this year: 32
Title Author Rating Notes Gods and Robots: Myths, Machines, and Ancient Dreams of Technology Adrienne Mayor C+ Enjoyable read highlighting the history of machines and their interactions with man. Planet Narnia: The Seven Heavens in the Imagination of C. S. Lewis Michael Ward A Amazing work suggesting a compelling interpretive framework for The Chronicles of Narnia. The Horse and His Boy C.</description></item><item><title>2020 Reading List</title><link>https://hightower.space/reading-list/2020-reading-list/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hightower.space/reading-list/2020-reading-list/</guid><description>(Top majority of this list is sorted alphabetically, but the tail is chronological)
Books read this year: 57
Title Author Rating A Right Conception of Sin Richard S. Taylor B Amusing Ourselves to Death Neil Postman B+ An Infinite Journey: Growing towards Christlikeness Andrew M. Davis C+ An Introduction to Logic H. W. B. Joseph C Art and Visual Perception: A Psychology of the Creative Eye Rudolf Arnheim B+ Baptism: Its mode and its subjects Alexander Carson B Crazy Busy Kevin Deyoung A Create vs.</description></item><item><title>2019 Reading List</title><link>https://hightower.space/reading-list/2019-reading-list/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hightower.space/reading-list/2019-reading-list/</guid><description>Telling the Truth: Evangelizing Postmoderns (D. A. Carson) Techniques and Assumptions in Jewish Exegesis Before 70 CE (Edward A. Goldman - link) Current Hermeneutical Trends: Toward Explanation or Obfuscation? (Robert L. Thomas - link) Hermeneutics and The Theological Task (Walter C. Kaiser, Jr. - link) The Postmodern Condition (Jean-François Lyotard) Towards a Theory of Software Development Expertise (Sebastian Baltes, Stephan Diehl - link and link) Hermeneutics of New Perspective on Paul (Robert L.</description></item><item><title>2018 Reading List</title><link>https://hightower.space/reading-list/2018-reading-list/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hightower.space/reading-list/2018-reading-list/</guid><description>A Guide to Prayer (Isaac Watts) Proof: Finding Freedom through the Intoxicating Joy of Irresistible Grace (Daniel Montgomery, Timothy Paul Jones) Long Before Luther: Tracing the Heart of the Gospel From Christ to the Reformation (Nathan Busenitz) Computers and Procrastination: The Peril and the Promise (Nick Breems) A Short History of the Interpretation of the Bible (Robert Grant) Praying the Bible (Donald S. Whitney) Politics and the English Language (George Orwell) Wuthering Heights (Emily Brontë) The Strenuous Life (A speech by Theodore Roosevelt) The Consolation of Philosophy (Boethius) Romans in the Greek New Testament for the English reader (Kenneth Samuel Wuest) The Prince and the Pauper (Mark Twain) Religious Affections (Jonathan Edwards) The Consequences of Ideas (R.</description></item></channel></rss>