<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Serverless on Floyd Hightower</title><link>https://hightower.space/tags/serverless/</link><description>Recent content in Serverless on Floyd Hightower</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://hightower.space/tags/serverless/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Frustrations When Using Cloud Functions</title><link>https://hightower.space/posts/cloud-functions-non-starter/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hightower.space/posts/cloud-functions-non-starter/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been examining Google Cloud&amp;rsquo;s serverless compute options.
I&amp;rsquo;ve been trying to use Cloud Functions, but have found them extrodinarily frustrating.
My problems are:
Slow feedback loop Slow feedback loops kill a dev&amp;rsquo;s effectiveness&amp;hellip; when deploying a new cloud function, it takes ≈ 30-40 seconds before one knows if something has failed - this is a long time to get feedback on a change One really can&amp;rsquo;t reasonably use cloud functions in the GUI - one would have to develop and test locally to make any workflow possible A ton of clicking just to see what has gone wrong If something does go wrong, (after waiting the 30-40 seconds to see that it has failed), one then has to click through a number of tabs/pages to view the logs&amp;hellip; this is really frustrating for devs who are used to not having to take their hands off the keyboard Odd UX when deploy fails When a deploy fails and one tries to edit the function, one will find that the function is not the most recent version of the function&amp;hellip; it&amp;rsquo;s the previously deployed version of the function!</description></item><item><title>GCP Serverless Compute Options Overview</title><link>https://hightower.space/posts/gcp-serverless-compute-options/</link><pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hightower.space/posts/gcp-serverless-compute-options/</guid><description>Intro This is a brief overview of the Serverless Compute Options in GCP.
After reading this post, I hope you are:
Familiar with the main options (at a high-level) Understand some main use-cases for each option Have a limited understanding of what it looks like to work with a service in each product The google docs on these subjects are really helpful&amp;hellip; I strongly recommend reading through them.</description></item></channel></rss>