<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Python on Floyd Hightower</title><link>https://hightower.space/tags/python/</link><description>Recent content in Python on Floyd Hightower</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://hightower.space/tags/python/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Simplified Scale Game</title><link>https://hightower.space/posts/scale_game_1/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hightower.space/posts/scale_game_1/</guid><description>Simplified Scale Game As I&amp;rsquo;m exploring machine learning, I have found it helpful to have a simple game I can use as a context in which to test ideas. This blog post describes one such game. I call it the &amp;ldquo;Scale Game&amp;rdquo;. The version I&amp;rsquo;m going to describe is the simplified version of the game.
The game works as follows:
There are two players (players &amp;lsquo;a&amp;rsquo; and &amp;lsquo;b&amp;rsquo;) Each player in the game gets one turn Each player makes his/her turn simultaneously (at least without knowledge of the other player&amp;rsquo;s move) Each player starts with ten marbles and ten dollars Each marble weighs one unit Each player chooses how many marbles of his/her marbles to place on his/her side of the scale Here are some rules we&amp;rsquo;ll start with, but will change over time:</description></item><item><title>Simple, Non-blocking, Push/Pull Example with ZeroMQ</title><link>https://hightower.space/posts/zeromq-push-pull/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hightower.space/posts/zeromq-push-pull/</guid><description>Intro While working on TotalEmail, I ran across a situation in which we needed to make a non-blocking request (a request where the client makes the request without waiting or expecting a response). To accomplish this, I started looking into ZeroMQ. ZeroMQ is amazing! It is very well-structured and generalizes the problem of messaging between machines very effectively.
While the ZeroMQ documentation is extensive, it is easy (at least for me) to get lost in the docs and forget the simplicity and elegance of ZeroMQ.</description></item></channel></rss>