<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Books on Floyd Hightower</title><link>https://hightower.space/tags/books/</link><description>Recent content in Books on Floyd Hightower</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://hightower.space/tags/books/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>2022 Mental Diet Log</title><link>https://hightower.space/posts/2022-reading-list/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hightower.space/posts/2022-reading-list/</guid><description>Books read in 2022: 7 Lord of the Rings: The Fellowship of the Ring [B&amp;#43;] Author(s): J. R. Tolkien Notes: I enjoy this series more and more each time I read it. This time, I noticed how the adventure begins right in Hobbiton as Frodo is almost caught on a number of occasions. The movies scale the danger as the adventure goes on, but the books introduce the danger right from the start Crucial Conversations: Tools for Talking When Stakes Are High [B&amp;#43;] Author(s): Joseph Grenny Ron McMillan Al Switzler Kerry Patterson Notes: I think this book is a &amp;lsquo;must-read&amp;rsquo; for everyone and worth reading regularly.</description></item><item><title>2021 Mental Diet Log</title><link>https://hightower.space/posts/2021-reading-list/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hightower.space/posts/2021-reading-list/</guid><description>Books read in 2021: 72 Gods and Robots: Myths, Machines, and Ancient Dreams of Technology [C&amp;#43;] Author(s): Adrienne Mayor Notes: Enjoyable read highlighting the history of machines and their interactions with man. Planet Narnia: The Seven Heavens in the Imagination of C. S. Lewis [B] Author(s): Michael Ward Notes: Amazing work suggesting a compelling interpretive framework for The Chronicles of Narnia.</description></item><item><title>2020 Reading List</title><link>https://hightower.space/posts/2020-reading-list/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hightower.space/posts/2020-reading-list/</guid><description>(Top majority of this list is sorted alphabetically, but the tail is chronological)
Books read in 2020: 58 Gods and Robots: Myths, Machines, and Ancient Dreams of Technology [C&amp;#43;] Author(s): Adrienne Mayor Notes: Enjoyable read highlighting the history of machines and their interactions with man. A Right Conception of Sin [B] Author(s): Richard S. Taylor Amusing Ourselves to Death [B&amp;#43;] Author(s): Neil Postman An Infinite Journey: Growing towards Christlikeness [C&amp;#43;] Author(s): Andrew M.</description></item><item><title>2019 Reading List</title><link>https://hightower.space/posts/2019-reading-list/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hightower.space/posts/2019-reading-list/</guid><description>Telling the Truth: Evangelizing Postmoderns (D. A. Carson) Techniques and Assumptions in Jewish Exegesis Before 70 CE (Edward A. Goldman - link) Current Hermeneutical Trends: Toward Explanation or Obfuscation? (Robert L. Thomas - link) Hermeneutics and The Theological Task (Walter C. Kaiser, Jr. - link) The Postmodern Condition (Jean-François Lyotard) Towards a Theory of Software Development Expertise (Sebastian Baltes, Stephan Diehl - link and link) Hermeneutics of New Perspective on Paul (Robert L.</description></item><item><title>2018 Reading List</title><link>https://hightower.space/posts/2018-reading-list/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hightower.space/posts/2018-reading-list/</guid><description>A Guide to Prayer (Isaac Watts) Proof: Finding Freedom through the Intoxicating Joy of Irresistible Grace (Daniel Montgomery, Timothy Paul Jones) Long Before Luther: Tracing the Heart of the Gospel From Christ to the Reformation (Nathan Busenitz) Computers and Procrastination: The Peril and the Promise (Nick Breems) A Short History of the Interpretation of the Bible (Robert Grant) Praying the Bible (Donald S. Whitney) Politics and the English Language (George Orwell) Wuthering Heights (Emily Brontë) The Strenuous Life (A speech by Theodore Roosevelt) The Consolation of Philosophy (Boethius) Romans in the Greek New Testament for the English reader (Kenneth Samuel Wuest) The Prince and the Pauper (Mark Twain) Religious Affections (Jonathan Edwards) The Consequences of Ideas (R.</description></item></channel></rss>