<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Frustration on Floyd</title><link>https://hightower.space/tags/frustration/</link><description>Recent content in Frustration on Floyd</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://hightower.space/tags/frustration/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Frustrations When Using Cloud Functions</title><link>https://hightower.space/posts/cloud-functions-non-starter/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hightower.space/posts/cloud-functions-non-starter/</guid><description>&lt;p>I&amp;rsquo;ve been &lt;a href="https://hightower.space/posts/gcp-serverless-compute-options/">examining&lt;/a> Google Cloud&amp;rsquo;s serverless compute options.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I&amp;rsquo;ve been trying to use Cloud Functions, but have found them extrodinarily frustrating.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>My problems are:&lt;/p>
&lt;ol>
&lt;li>Slow feedback loop
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Slow feedback loops kill a dev&amp;rsquo;s effectiveness&amp;hellip; when deploying a new cloud function, it takes ≈ 30-40 seconds before one knows if something has failed - this is a &lt;em>long&lt;/em> time to get feedback on a change&lt;/li>
&lt;li>One really can&amp;rsquo;t reasonably use cloud functions in the GUI - one would have to develop and test locally to make any workflow possible&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>A &lt;em>ton&lt;/em> of clicking just to see what has gone wrong
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>If something does go wrong, (after waiting the 30-40 seconds to see that it has failed), one then has to click through a number of tabs/pages to view the logs&amp;hellip; this is really frustrating for devs who are used to not having to take their hands off the keyboard&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Odd UX when deploy fails
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>When a deploy fails and one tries to edit the function, one will find that the function is &lt;em>not&lt;/em> the most recent version of the function&amp;hellip; it&amp;rsquo;s the &lt;em>previously deployed&lt;/em> version of the function! So, if I write ten lines of code in a function, try to deploy it, and the deploy fails, I have lost the ten lines I added b/c the deploy failed!&lt;/li>
&lt;li>This, in my opinion, violates the &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Principle_of_least_astonishment">principle of least astonishment&lt;/a> and makes working with functions in the GUI absolutely impractical&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;/li>
&lt;/ol>
&lt;p>All in all, I was disappointed to find Cloud Functions frustrating and largely impractical.
It is marketed as an &amp;rsquo;easy&amp;rsquo;, &amp;lsquo;simple&amp;rsquo; way to run code, but I&amp;rsquo;ve found it is more hassle unless one is using docker to develop locally and deploying to a cloud function by pushing to a git repo.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>