<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>English on Floyd</title><link>https://hightower.space/tags/english/</link><description>Recent content in English on Floyd</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 19 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://hightower.space/tags/english/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>My Words</title><link>https://hightower.space/posts/my-words/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hightower.space/posts/my-words/</guid><description>&lt;p>The words we use open doors for us to think new thoughts. Personally, I agree with a weak hypothesis branch of the &lt;a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Linguistic_relativity">Sapir–Whorf hypothesis&lt;/a> as supported by the &amp;ldquo;&lt;a href="http://www.pnas.org/content/104/19/7780">Russian blues&lt;/a>&amp;rdquo; experiment. Because I believe that words are powerful and I have noticed that our language does not have words for some ideas and things I would like to articulate, I have invented (sometimes stolen from other languages) the following words:&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="lachem">Lachem&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;em>Noun, the &amp;ldquo;ch&amp;rdquo; is a gutteral as in the word &amp;ldquo;loch&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em>: A member of a set whose name and/or characteristics (usually just the name) has come to described the whole set. For example, Kleenexes are a lachem because Kleenex is just one member of the set of all facial tissue brands, yet the name has come to characterize the entire set of facial tissues.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="lamech">Lamech&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;em>Noun, the &amp;ldquo;ch&amp;rdquo; is a gutteral as in the word &amp;ldquo;loch&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em>: A member of a set to which the parent set is viewed as having shrunk. An example is the term &lt;a href="https://hightower.space/thoughts/gui-vs-ui/">&amp;lsquo;UI&amp;rsquo;&lt;/a>.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="machem">Machem&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;em>Noun, the &amp;ldquo;ch&amp;rdquo; is a gutteral as in the word &amp;ldquo;loch&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em>: A member of a set which is viewed as being distinct from its parent set. For example, malware is a subset of computer programs, but malware is often viewed by the general public as distinct from &amp;rsquo;normal&amp;rsquo; computer programs. Therefore, malware could be called a machem.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="suvia">Suvia&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;em>Noun&lt;/em>: A journey or travel in the rain.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="solvia">Solvia&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;em>Noun&lt;/em>: A journey or travel in the direction of the sun (usually the setting sun).&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="parea">Parea&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;em>Noun&lt;/em>: Has the same meaning as the Greek word from which it is transliterated: a group of friends who gather to enjoy nothing else but sharing their life experiences, philosophies, values, and ideas.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="egan">Egan&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;em>Noun&lt;/em>: One of your ideas which you find has already been described, accomplished, or articulated by someone else.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;em>Verb&lt;/em>: The act performed when someone describes, accomplishes, or articulates an idea that you had. For example, &amp;ldquo;She is going to &lt;em>egan&lt;/em> someone.&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;I have been &lt;em>eganed&lt;/em>!&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="nage">Nage&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;em>Noun, pronounced with a soft &amp;lsquo;g&amp;rsquo;&lt;/em>: The feeling when you realize that one of your ideas is an egan (see the two words above). This sensation is simultaneously an honor (because you had a good idea) and a disappointment (because the egan is already taken).&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="wouldings">Wouldings&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;em>Noun&lt;/em>: This word, invented by &lt;a href="https://hightower.space/tags/jonathan-edwards">Jonathan Edwards&lt;/a>, refers to &amp;ldquo;very weak inclinations which do not represent genuine convictions and do not issue in action&amp;rdquo;&lt;sup>&lt;a href="#footnote1">1&lt;/a>&lt;/sup>&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="bundling">Bundling&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;em>Verb&lt;/em>: The action performed when one wears clothing appropriate for the weather you would &lt;em>like&lt;/em> to have rather than the weather you actually have.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="strofe">Strofe&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;em>Noun&lt;/em>: Derived from &amp;ldquo;&lt;strong>str&lt;/strong>anger &lt;strong>o&lt;/strong>n road &lt;strong>f&lt;/strong>requently &lt;strong>e&lt;/strong>ncountered&amp;rdquo; refers to a stranger that you keep seeing while traveling.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="notes">Notes&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>&lt;a id="footnote1">1. &lt;/a>This quotation is taken from footnote #2 here: Edwards, Jonathan, Perry Miller, John E. Smith, and Harry S. Stout. &lt;em>The Works of Jonathan Edwards. Religious Affections&lt;/em>. New Haven: Yale University Press, 1966, 99.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>