<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on Floyd Hightower</title><link>https://hightower.space/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Floyd Hightower</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://hightower.space/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>2022 Mental Diet Log</title><link>https://hightower.space/posts/2022-reading-list/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hightower.space/posts/2022-reading-list/</guid><description>Books read in 2022: 2 Lord of the Rings: The Fellowship of the Ring [B&amp;#43;] Author(s): J. R. Tolkien Notes: I enjoy this series more and more each time I read it. This time, I noticed how the adventure begins right in Hobbiton as Frodo is almost caught on a number of occasions. The movies scale the danger as the adventure goes on, but the books introduce the danger right from the start Crucial Conversations: Tools for Talking When Stakes Are High [A&amp;#43;] Author(s): Joseph Grenny Ron McMillan Al Switzler Kerry Patterson Notes: I think this book is a &amp;lsquo;must-read&amp;rsquo; for everyone and is a rare book I will try to read every year or so.</description></item><item><title>Formulas for Financial Independence</title><link>https://hightower.space/posts/financial-independence-formulas-1/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hightower.space/posts/financial-independence-formulas-1/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Investigating Interest</title><link>https://hightower.space/posts/interest-investigation/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hightower.space/posts/interest-investigation/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Mom and Dad Tips</title><link>https://hightower.space/posts/mom-and-dad-tips/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hightower.space/posts/mom-and-dad-tips/</guid><description>Tips Number Mom Dad 1 ??? Always bring more water than you need 2 Cutting onions can make you cry ??? 3 ??? A book read and applied is better than ten books simply read and one hundred books neither read nor applied. 4 Make your bed! Responsibility starts at home Some things are worth your time; some aren&amp;rsquo;t</description></item><item><title>Interactive Writing System</title><link>https://hightower.space/posts/interactive-writing-system/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hightower.space/posts/interactive-writing-system/</guid><description>Interactive Writing System What are interactive systems? I will not, in this blog post, consider the essential and non-essential properties of interactive systems. I will simply assert that an essential characteristic of interactive systems is a short feedback loop.
The problem For some reason, we (as humanity and software developers) have relegated ourselves to static systems and tools. We have eschewed interactivity. In this blog post, I will not examine why this is the case, but will note examples of this problem and describe a system which would introduce interactivity to the technical blog writing world.</description></item><item><title>Simplified Scale Game</title><link>https://hightower.space/posts/scale_game_1/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hightower.space/posts/scale_game_1/</guid><description>Simplified Scale Game As I&amp;rsquo;m exploring machine learning, I have found it helpful to have a simple game I can use as a context in which to test ideas. This blog post describes one such game. I call it the &amp;ldquo;Scale Game&amp;rdquo;. The version I&amp;rsquo;m going to describe is the simplified version of the game.
The game works as follows:
There are two players (players &amp;lsquo;a&amp;rsquo; and &amp;lsquo;b&amp;rsquo;) Each player in the game gets one turn Each player makes his/her turn simultaneously (at least without knowledge of the other player&amp;rsquo;s move) Each player starts with ten marbles and ten dollars Each marble weighs one unit Each player chooses how many marbles of his/her marbles to place on his/her side of the scale Here are some rules we&amp;rsquo;ll start with, but will change over time:</description></item><item><title>Conjecture on n-sided Numbers and Their Sums</title><link>https://hightower.space/posts/conjecture-on-n-sided-numbers/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hightower.space/posts/conjecture-on-n-sided-numbers/</guid><description>While reading The Most Beautiful Mathematical Formulas: An Entertaining Look at the Most Insightful, Useful, and Quirky Theorems of All Time, I came across Lagrange&amp;rsquo;s four-square theorem:
We can represent every natural number as the sum of, at most, four squares.
For example, we can represent 27 as:
16 + 9 + 1 + 1 or
4^2 + 3^3 + 1^2 + 1^2 As I was reading about this, I came up with the following conjecture.</description></item><item><title>Informed, Random Walk</title><link>https://hightower.space/posts/informed-random-walk/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hightower.space/posts/informed-random-walk/</guid><description>Background Stripe Press published a beautiful copy of &amp;ldquo;The Art of Doing Science and Engineering&amp;rdquo; by Richard Hamming:
Aside from being a wonderful read, the cover of this book (which is an apt analogy for the learning process) features an intriguing pattern. As I was reading the book while traveling, I was nerd sniped into designing an algorithm which would make such a pattern. This post is an explication of my solution.</description></item><item><title>2021 Mental Diet Log</title><link>https://hightower.space/posts/2021-reading-list/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hightower.space/posts/2021-reading-list/</guid><description>Books read in 2021: 72 Gods and Robots: Myths, Machines, and Ancient Dreams of Technology [C&amp;#43;] Author(s): Adrienne Mayor Notes: Enjoyable read highlighting the history of machines and their interactions with man. Planet Narnia: The Seven Heavens in the Imagination of C. S. Lewis [B] Author(s): Michael Ward Notes: Amazing work suggesting a compelling interpretive framework for The Chronicles of Narnia.</description></item><item><title>2020 Reading List</title><link>https://hightower.space/posts/2020-reading-list/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hightower.space/posts/2020-reading-list/</guid><description>(Top majority of this list is sorted alphabetically, but the tail is chronological)
Books read in 2020: 58 Gods and Robots: Myths, Machines, and Ancient Dreams of Technology [C&amp;#43;] Author(s): Adrienne Mayor Notes: Enjoyable read highlighting the history of machines and their interactions with man. A Right Conception of Sin [B] Author(s): Richard S. Taylor Amusing Ourselves to Death [B&amp;#43;] Author(s): Neil Postman An Infinite Journey: Growing towards Christlikeness [C&amp;#43;] Author(s): Andrew M.</description></item><item><title>Simple, Non-blocking, Push/Pull Example with ZeroMQ</title><link>https://hightower.space/posts/zeromq-push-pull/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hightower.space/posts/zeromq-push-pull/</guid><description>Intro While working on TotalEmail, I ran across a situation in which we needed to make a non-blocking request (a request where the client makes the request without waiting or expecting a response). To accomplish this, I started looking into ZeroMQ. ZeroMQ is amazing! It is very well-structured and generalizes the problem of messaging between machines very effectively.
While the ZeroMQ documentation is extensive, it is easy (at least for me) to get lost in the docs and forget the simplicity and elegance of ZeroMQ.</description></item><item><title>Domain Squatting Math</title><link>https://hightower.space/posts/math-behind-domain-squatting/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hightower.space/posts/math-behind-domain-squatting/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;Compound interest is the eighth wonder of the world. He who understands it, earns it &amp;hellip; he who doesn&amp;rsquo;t &amp;hellip; pays it.&amp;rdquo;
― Albert Einstein
What is domain squatting? Domain squatting is when someone registers a domain name which looks like another domain name. Usually, the term &amp;ldquo;domain squatting&amp;rdquo; is used in a context where malicious intent is implied. For example, someone trying to steal passwords may register the domain name gooogle.</description></item><item><title>Conjecture on Resource Utilization</title><link>https://hightower.space/posts/resource-utilization/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hightower.space/posts/resource-utilization/</guid><description>We fifty-four were the masters of England! Twenty-five thousand men lay dead around us. But how treacherous is fortune! In a little while - say an hour - happened a thing, by my own fault, which - but I have no heart to write that. Let the record end here.1
1 - Written by "The Boss" (from A Connecticut Yankee in King Arthur's Court) We were in a trap, you see - a trap of our own making&amp;hellip; we had conquered; in turn we were conquered.</description></item><item><title>HTML-to-JSON Conversion Library</title><link>https://hightower.space/posts/html-to-json/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hightower.space/posts/html-to-json/</guid><description>HTML-to-JSON Library I have a project here to convert HTML to JSON. You can find installation instructions here: https://gitlab.com/fhightower/html-to-json#installation.
The library can convert any/all html to json such that this:
&amp;lt;head&amp;gt; &amp;lt;title&amp;gt;Floyd Hightower&amp;#39;s Projects&amp;lt;/title&amp;gt; &amp;lt;meta charset=&amp;#34;UTF-8&amp;#34;&amp;gt; &amp;lt;meta name=&amp;#34;description&amp;#34; content=&amp;#34;Floyd Hightower&amp;amp;#39;s Projects&amp;#34;&amp;gt; &amp;lt;meta name=&amp;#34;keywords&amp;#34; content=&amp;#34;projects,fhightower,Floyd,Hightower&amp;#34;&amp;gt; &amp;lt;/head&amp;gt; becomes:
{ &amp;#34;head&amp;#34;: [ { &amp;#34;title&amp;#34;: [ { &amp;#34;value&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;Floyd Hightower\&amp;#39;s Projects&amp;#34; }], &amp;#34;meta&amp;#34;: [ { &amp;#34;attributes&amp;#34;: { &amp;#34;charset&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;UTF-8&amp;#34; } }, { &amp;#34;attributes&amp;#34;: { &amp;#34;name&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;description&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;content&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;Floyd Hightower\&amp;#39;s Projects&amp;#34; } }, { &amp;#34;attributes&amp;#34;: { &amp;#34;name&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;keywords&amp;#34;, &amp;#34;content&amp;#34;: &amp;#34;projects,fhightower,Floyd,Hightower&amp;#34; } }] }] } And you can tell it to only convert html tables in which case it will convert tables and use the table headings as the keys for the resulting json (this is described in depth here).</description></item><item><title>Analysis of Obfuscated PHP Malware</title><link>https://hightower.space/posts/php-malware-analysis-jan-29-part-1/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hightower.space/posts/php-malware-analysis-jan-29-part-1/</guid><description>Updated on February 27, 2019.
I am monitoring the php decoder site here and was alerted when the decoded php here had a String.fromCharCode command in it. After decoding the character code (104, 116, 116, 112, 115, 58, 47, 47, 103, 101, 116, 109, 121, 99, 111, 110, 102, 105, 103, 112, 108, 101, 97, 115, 101, 46, 99, 111, 109, 47, 103, 101, 116, 46, 112, 104, 112)1 --, this produced https://getmyconfigplease[.</description></item><item><title>Running Gitbook on Gitlab</title><link>https://hightower.space/posts/gitbook-on-gitlab/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hightower.space/posts/gitbook-on-gitlab/</guid><description>Here&amp;rsquo;s how to run a gitbook in gitlab pages:
Create a repo in Gitlab Clone the template here Add the following file as .gitlab-ci.yml and push to gitlab: # requiring the environment of NodeJS 6.12.x image: node:6.12 # add 'node_modules' to cache for speeding up builds cache: paths: - node_modules/ # Node modules and dependencies before_script: - npm install gitbook-cli -g # install gitbook - gitbook fetch latest # fetch latest stable version - gitbook install # add any requested plugins in book.</description></item><item><title>Fascinating Flags</title><link>https://hightower.space/posts/fascinating-flags/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hightower.space/posts/fascinating-flags/</guid><description> https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Flag_of_Greece - Fascinating because of the supposed connection with the phrase &amp;ldquo;Ελευθερία ή Θάνατος&amp;rdquo; https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Flag_of_Bikini_Atoll - Fascinating historical significance behind this flag https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Flag_of_Bangladesh - Fascinating because the central circle is off-centered so that it appears in the middle when flying from a pole/mast https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Tehuelche_people#/media/File:Bandiera_tehuelche.jpg - This one is just oddly laid out. I like it as it is very unusual and eye-catching.</description></item><item><title>2019 Reading List</title><link>https://hightower.space/posts/2019-reading-list/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hightower.space/posts/2019-reading-list/</guid><description>Telling the Truth: Evangelizing Postmoderns (D. A. Carson) Techniques and Assumptions in Jewish Exegesis Before 70 CE (Edward A. Goldman - link) Current Hermeneutical Trends: Toward Explanation or Obfuscation? (Robert L. Thomas - link) Hermeneutics and The Theological Task (Walter C. Kaiser, Jr. - link) The Postmodern Condition (Jean-François Lyotard) Towards a Theory of Software Development Expertise (Sebastian Baltes, Stephan Diehl - link and link) Hermeneutics of New Perspective on Paul (Robert L.</description></item><item><title>A Question on Pragmaticism</title><link>https://hightower.space/posts/pragmaticism-question/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hightower.space/posts/pragmaticism-question/</guid><description>I was recently reading about Pragmaticism (for an article I wrote here: Why Christians Must be Wary of Pragmaticism), and found the following definition in the Century Dictionary from 1909:
pragmaticism (prag-mat′ i-sizm), n. [pragmatic + ism.] A special and limited form of pragmatism, in which the pragmatism is restricted to the determining of the meaning of concepts (particularly of philosophic concepts) by consideration of the experimental differences in the conduct of life which would conceivably result from the affirmation or denial of the meaning in question.</description></item><item><title>Playbook Friday Blogs</title><link>https://hightower.space/posts/tc-pb-friday-blog-posts/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hightower.space/posts/tc-pb-friday-blog-posts/</guid><description>The following playbooks have been featured in a ThreatConnect &amp;ldquo;Playbook Friday&amp;rdquo; blog post:
https://threatconnect.com/blog/google-alerts-rss-reader/ https://threatconnect.com/blog/robtex-asn-query-ip-query/ https://threatconnect.com/blog/task-management/</description></item><item><title>GUI vs. UI</title><link>https://hightower.space/posts/gui-vs-ui/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hightower.space/posts/gui-vs-ui/</guid><description>I believe words are important.1 I recently caught myself saying something I consider dangerous for the way we think about computing and programming. I found my self saying &amp;ldquo;UI&amp;rdquo; (which is short for &amp;ldquo;User Interface&amp;rdquo;) to describe a &amp;ldquo;GUI&amp;rdquo; (a &amp;ldquo;Graphical User Interface&amp;rdquo;). UI is a broad category which encompasses multiple ways a user may interface with a system. A GUI is a specific instance of UI which relies on &amp;lsquo;visual metaphors&amp;rsquo; to communicate information to a user and allow the user to interact with the underlying system (the most ubiquitous example of a GUI is a website).</description></item><item><title>My Words</title><link>https://hightower.space/posts/my-words/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hightower.space/posts/my-words/</guid><description>The words we use open doors for us to think new thoughts. Personally, I agree with a weak hypothesis branch of the Sapir–Whorf hypothesis as supported by the &amp;ldquo;Russian blues&amp;rdquo; experiment. Because I believe that words are powerful and I have noticed that our language does not have words for some ideas and things I would like to articulate, I have invented (sometimes stolen from other languages) the following words:</description></item><item><title>Rome Wasn't Built in a Day</title><link>https://hightower.space/posts/great-things-take-time/</link><pubDate>Sat, 18 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hightower.space/posts/great-things-take-time/</guid><description>I could say a lot on this subject, but for now, I&amp;rsquo;ll make this quick (which is ironic in light of the topic at hand). I believe that doing things of great value takes time. This applies to software, research, education, business, relationships, sports, and every area of life. I experience this reality on a daily basis as my passion is writing software. Good software and powerful tools just take time to design, develop, and refine.</description></item><item><title>A Definitive Guide for Ignoring Sublime Linter Errors</title><link>https://hightower.space/posts/sublime-linter-ignore-guide/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hightower.space/posts/sublime-linter-ignore-guide/</guid><description>I found it very difficult to ignore sublime linter errors in Sublime Text, so this guide shows how to ignore these errors easily. If you have feedback, updates, or additions, please let me know (or raise an issue).
Ignoring Linter Errors Example To ignore linter errors, open Sublime Text and navigate to Preferences &amp;gt; Package Settings &amp;gt; SublimeLinter &amp;gt; Settings. This will open a Sublime Text window with the default sublime linter settings on the left and your user settings on the right.</description></item><item><title>Let Your Ideas See the Light of Day</title><link>https://hightower.space/posts/light-of-day/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hightower.space/posts/light-of-day/</guid><description>It is a deeply held principle of mine that beliefs and ideas are strongest when they have been tested and exposed to the proverbial &amp;lsquo;light of day&amp;rsquo;. We have a tendency to cloister our beliefs and new ideas within the comfortable walls of our own minds. When we do this, we are missing out on the criticism, critique, and dialog that makes ideas powerful and robust.
Ideas which are not exposed to the real world are like a cardboard box; they can withstand minimal pressure from certain directions, but are not ready to hold up the weight of careful scrutiny.</description></item><item><title>Questions for QA</title><link>https://hightower.space/posts/questions-for-qa/</link><pubDate>Wed, 25 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hightower.space/posts/questions-for-qa/</guid><description>In doing QA-esque things for friends and coworkers, I have noticed that some people do not have a good sense of how to &amp;lsquo;QA&amp;rsquo; something. I compiled a short list of questions below that I ask myself.
Testing Inputs Does the system handle1&amp;hellip;
1 - Defining the word "handle" can be tricky and the definition and standards change from project to project. In most projects, a system can be said to "</description></item><item><title/><link>https://hightower.space/posts/leaves-for-money/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hightower.space/posts/leaves-for-money/</guid><description/></item><item><title>JavaScript Puzzles: How Well do you Know Javascript?</title><link>https://hightower.space/posts/javascript-puzzles/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hightower.space/posts/javascript-puzzles/</guid><description>Here are a couple of fun Javascript puzzles I&amp;rsquo;ve created/found to demonstrate important Javascript gotchas. There are answers/explanations near the bottom of the page.
Puzzles Variable Scoping As I&amp;rsquo;m learning Typescript, I was reading through the docs and ran across a fascinating little code snippet demonstrating variable scoping gotchas in javascript. The question was:
What is the output of the code below?
for (var i = 0; i &amp;lt; 10; i++) { setTimeout(function() { console.</description></item><item><title>Logic Operations</title><link>https://hightower.space/posts/logic_operations/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hightower.space/posts/logic_operations/</guid><description>NOT A: 0.00
B: 0.00
= 1−A1 - A1−A
= 1 - 0.00
= 1.00
AND A: 0.00
B: 0.00
= A∗BA * BA∗B
=0.00 *0.00
=0.00
NAND A: 0.00
B: 0.00
= 1−(A∗B)1 - (A * B)1−(A∗B)
=1 - (0.00 *0.00)
=1.00
OR A: 0.00
B: 0.00
= A+B−A∗BA + B - A * BA+B−A∗B
= 0.00 + 0.</description></item><item><title>Collatz Conjecture Playground</title><link>https://hightower.space/posts/collatz-conjecture/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hightower.space/posts/collatz-conjecture/</guid><description>Starting value: 10.00
Found solution in: 6.00 steps
1.02.03.04.05.06.051015xy0101521638445261Loading... This was written using the Idyll markup language for creating interactive documents. The Idyll code to create this page is:
Starting value: [var name:&amp;quot;number&amp;quot; value:10 /] [Range value:number min:1 max:100 /] [Display value:number /] [var name:&amp;quot;createJson&amp;quot; value:`function(max, step, number) { var data = []; function iterate(max, step, number) { var newNumber; if (number % 2 === 0) { newNumber = number / 2; } else { newNumber = 3*number + 1; } if (newNumber !</description></item><item><title>2018 Reading List</title><link>https://hightower.space/posts/2018-reading-list/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hightower.space/posts/2018-reading-list/</guid><description>A Guide to Prayer (Isaac Watts) Proof: Finding Freedom through the Intoxicating Joy of Irresistible Grace (Daniel Montgomery, Timothy Paul Jones) Long Before Luther: Tracing the Heart of the Gospel From Christ to the Reformation (Nathan Busenitz) Computers and Procrastination: The Peril and the Promise (Nick Breems) A Short History of the Interpretation of the Bible (Robert Grant) Praying the Bible (Donald S. Whitney) Politics and the English Language (George Orwell) Wuthering Heights (Emily Brontë) The Strenuous Life (A speech by Theodore Roosevelt) The Consolation of Philosophy (Boethius) Romans in the Greek New Testament for the English reader (Kenneth Samuel Wuest) The Prince and the Pauper (Mark Twain) Religious Affections (Jonathan Edwards) The Consequences of Ideas (R.</description></item><item><title>Defining Sports</title><link>https://hightower.space/posts/defining-sports/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hightower.space/posts/defining-sports/</guid><description>If you were to do some research on the etymology of the word &amp;ldquo;sport&amp;rdquo;, you would find that the word has its root in the idea of pleasurable, enjoyable activities, games, or flirtations that amuse and temporarily divert one&amp;rsquo;s attention1. I am arguing, however, that this definition has changed with the advent of professional sports. With the rise of professional baseball and football in the first third of the 20th century, people began to view sports as an important part of culture.</description></item><item><title>The Smith of the gods is Lame</title><link>https://hightower.space/posts/the-smith-of-the-gods-is-lame/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hightower.space/posts/the-smith-of-the-gods-is-lame/</guid><description>The Smith of the gods is Lame The smith of the gods is lame. His feet have seen no battles. His legs have won no races. The smith of the gods is lame.
The smith of the gods is lame. His hands have won more battles than any other man, for tho his feet not bring him glory, his skill, his hands have stood. The smith of the gods is lame.</description></item></channel></rss>