<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Abortion on Floyd</title><link>https://hightower.space/tags/abortion/</link><description>Recent content in Abortion on Floyd</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://hightower.space/tags/abortion/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Letter to my Employer on Their Abortion Policy</title><link>https://hightower.space/posts/letter-on-abortion-policy/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hightower.space/posts/letter-on-abortion-policy/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="background">Background&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Below is an anonymized version of a letter I shared with my employer to clarify their position and seek a less partisan policy. All references to my company have been replaced with &amp;ldquo;Acme&amp;rdquo; and any edited portions are surrounded with [square brackets].&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="my-letter">My Letter&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>In this document, I express questions and concerns about the “New Reproductive Rights Travel Benefit”[1] in the form of two contradictions. Both contradictions exist between the decision to reimburse travel to abortion and the original announcement’s statement: “We at [Acme] have worked to create a welcoming space for all and believe in our guiding principles of Respecting Others”. I believe these two contradictions demonstrate that this partisan policy will not create a “welcoming space for all” and will have the unintended consequence of excluding certain groups from access to a “welcoming space” and respect.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Because abortion[2] is such an immensely important and impactful matter, affecting the lives of millions of mothers and the unborn (not to mention their families), I consider it necessary to express these contradictions with the hope of clarifying [Acme]’s position on these issues and seeking a less partisan policy which is more inclusive and respectful of diverse ideologies and people.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="contradiction-1-regarding-pro-life-employees">Contradiction 1: Regarding Pro-Life Employees&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>In contradiction of the work to &amp;ldquo;create a welcoming space for all&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;our guiding principles of Respecting Others&amp;rdquo;, this policy does not create a welcoming space for pro-life employees nor does it respect them and their convictions. By reimbursing travel to get an abortion, [Acme] is effectively requiring that all employees who make the company profitable (hopefully all of them), facilitate the procurement of abortions - a behavior which is, by definition, antithetical to the moral convictions of pro-life employees. I am concerned that this policy, far from creating a &amp;ldquo;welcoming space for all&amp;rdquo;, forces many current and potential pro-life employees to choose between funding something they believe is morally wrong or leaving [Acme]. Is there a new policy we could enact which will create a more welcoming space for pro-life employees and does not corner them into this difficult dilemma?&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="contradiction-2-regarding-unborn-human-life-in-a-womb">Contradiction 2: Regarding Unborn, Human Life in a Womb&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>The second contradiction of the work to &amp;ldquo;create a welcoming space for all&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;our guiding principles of Respecting Others&amp;rdquo; is that this policy does not create a &amp;ldquo;welcoming space&amp;rdquo; for unborn life in a womb nor does it respect that life - it facilitates the killing of it. I recognize that some of my pro-abortion colleagues may object to this representation and I sincerely want to learn how they represent what happens during an abortion. That being said, until convinced otherwise, I take it as a biological fact that a successful abortion kills an unborn life. As such, there is a contradiction in claiming this policy will help &amp;ldquo;create a welcoming space for all&amp;rdquo; and respect others; it only respects those outside of the womb and guarantees no welcoming space and respect for life inside the womb.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The only way I know of to resolve this contradiction is to presuppose that unborn life in a womb is not inherently worthy of receiving a &amp;ldquo;welcoming space&amp;rdquo; and respect. Is [Acme] making this presupposition? If so, on what basis and by what authority does [Acme] affirm that life in a womb is not inherently worthy of a &amp;ldquo;welcoming space&amp;rdquo; and respect? Is [Acme], an e-commerce company, qualified to speak authoritatively and definitively on a contentious bioethical subject which is still being debated across the United States and in our Federal Government?&lt;/p>
&lt;p>If my suggested resolution of this contradiction is inaccurate, please explain how [Acme] resolves this contradiction. If [Acme] believes that unborn life in a womb is inherently worthy of receiving a &amp;ldquo;welcoming space&amp;rdquo; and respect, how can [Acme] justify this policy which deprives the unborn life of that which is supposedly inherent to it?&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="conclusion">Conclusion&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>In the stated mission to &amp;ldquo;create a welcoming space for all&amp;rdquo; (emphasis added) and respect others, [Acme] has defined the terms &amp;ldquo;all&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;others&amp;rdquo; so narrowly that I fear these statements are declarations of partisan support rather than inclusion and respect for diverse ideologies and individuals. I am concerned that the work to &amp;ldquo;create a welcoming space for all&amp;rdquo; (emphasis added) only applies to employees who are pro-abortion and family members outside of a womb. Similarly, when applying the principle of respecting others, [Acme] effectively excludes pro-life employees and unborn human lives inside a womb from the ‘others’ deemed worthy of respect.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I know this document will be very difficult to read for many, but I believe this moment requires candor and clarity on this immensely consequential topic. We must be willing to have hard conversations if we are to form a just, diverse, and inclusive company in which no one (whether inside or outside a womb) is excluded from the respect that is inherently due them and the welcoming space we seek to provide.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Respectfully,&lt;/p>
&lt;p>[Floyd]&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="footnotes">Footnotes&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>[1] - In the original document, there is a link to the announcement here, but this was removed as the announcement I&amp;rsquo;m referencing was made internally.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>[2] - In the original document, I have a footnote here noting that, when I refer to &amp;ldquo;abortion&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;abortions&amp;rdquo;, I am referring to abortions &lt;em>without&lt;/em> medical necessity; that is, abortions which are &lt;em>not&lt;/em> necessary to save the mother’s life. I note that there I am not aware of any states with restrictions on abortions for medical necessity and, therefore, assume that [Acme]’s policy of reimbursing travel to get abortions will primarily be used for abortions without medical necessity.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>